//Declare variable Questions

var questions [
    {
        Question: "Which type of values return a true of false statement?"
            answers: {
                 a:"Boolean"
                 b:"Empty Values"
                 c:"Strings"
                 d:"Numbers"
        }
        correctAnswer: "a" 
        }
    {
        Question: "Where is the link for JavaScript inserted into a Web Page?"
            answers: { 
                a:"footer"
                b:"header"
                c:"top of the body"
                d:"bottom of the body"
        }
        correctAnswer: "d"
        }
    
    {
        Question: "Which of the following is an example of a comparison operator?"
            answers: {
                   a:"*"
                   b:"&&"
                   c:"!="
                   d:"?:"
    }
        correctAnswer: "c"
    }
    {
        Question: "What happens if the tested condition is false?"
            answers: {
                  a:"The code's execution will be stopped"
                  b:"The code in the braces gets executed anyway"
                  c:"The code does nothing and moves to the next section"
                  d:"The code executes the section"
    }
        correctAnswer: "c"
    }
    {   
        Question: "What is the result of trying to reference an array member which does not exist?"
            Answers: {
                    a: "false"
                    b: "0"
                    c: "undefined"
                    d: "null"
                }
            correctAnwser: "c"

    }
    {
        Question: "An array has the length property, because it is:"
            Answers: {
                a: "an object"
                b: "a function"
                c: "a variable"
                d: "a element"
            }
                correctAnwser: "a"
            }
     {
        Question: "The concat method takes two arrays and:"
            Answers: {
                a: "combines them into 1 new array"
                b: "compares their members"
                c: "outputs them to the screen"
                d: "deletes the larger array"
            }
                correctAnwser: "a"
    }
    {
        Question: "In the Math Object, which of the following constants do not exist?"
            Answers: {
                a: "Math.PI",
                b: "Math.E",
                c: "Math.ABC",
                d: "Math.LN10",
            }
                correctAnwser: "c"
    }
    {
        Question: "In the Math Object, which of the following methods is used to calculate the square root?"
            Answers: {
                a: "round"
                b: "ceil"
                c: "sqrt"
                d: "root"
            }
                correctAnwser: "c"
    }
    {
        Question: "What does DOM stand for?"
            Answers: {
                a: "Document Object Model"
                b: "Document Orientation Model"
                c: "Definitive Orientation Model"
                d: "Definitive Object Model"
            }
                correctAnwser: "a"
    }
]